Inventory of the Public Information Office Press Releases, 1961 - 1978
Public Information Office Press Releases, 1961 - 1978
Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)
1000-168
8
9
The Public Relations Office, which was later called Office of Public Information and Publications, was responsible for communicating news and achievements at Wesleyan University to the local, state, and national media. This office was later folded into the University Relations department.
This collection of Public Information Press Releases is comprised of the press releases Wesleyan University sent out between 1961 and 1978. The press releases reported on the achievements of students and faculty, Wesleyan sports teams, and events on campus.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisitions Information
Transferred circa 1979.
Historical Note
The Public Relations Office, which was later called Office of Public Information and Publications, was responsible for communicating news and achievements at Wesleyan University to the local, state, and national media. This office was later folded into the University Relations department.
Collection Overview
This collection of Public Information Press Releases is comprised of the press releases Wesleyan University sent out between 1961 and 1978, mostly to Connecticut publications and occasionally to publications throughout the United States. Many of the press releases are about the Wesleyan athletic teams, including scores, upcoming games, individual achievements, and team statistics. Other press releases detail cultural and academic activities on campus, such as visiting lecturers and guest speakers, musical performances, plays, workshops, movies shown on campus, and lectures by and discussions with Wesleyan faculty. In May of each year, a press release was sent to the hometown paper of each graduating student and again in the fall for the incoming freshmen. Any announcements of awards given to students, either academic or athletic, were sent to hometown papers as well. Press releases also noted any information regarding achievements of faculty, including faculty receiving tenure and announcements of new faculty to Wesleyan.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Administration.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Faculty.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--History.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Students.; Press releases.; College sports--Connecticut--Wesleyan University, Middletown.
Detailed Description of the Collection
  - June 13, 1961-October 20, 1961 (Box 1)
  - October 20, 1961-December 6, 1961 (Box 1)
  - December 5, 1961-February 11, 1962 (Box 1)
  - February 5, 1962-March 8, 1962 (Box 1)
  - March 9, 1962- April 30, 1962 (Box 1)
  - May 2, 1962- June 17, 1962 (Box 1)
  - July 20, 1962-October 18, 1962 (Box 1)
  - October 20, 1962-November 16, 1962 (Box 1)
  - November 17, 1962-December 12, 1962 (Box 1)
  - January 8, 1963-February 18, 1963 (Box 1)
  - February 19, 1963-May 1, 1963 (Box 1)
  - May 1, 1963-June 2, 1963 (Box 1)
  - June 2, 1963-June 27, 1963 (Box 1)
  - July 3, 1963-September 9, 1963 (Box 1)
  - September 9, 1963-October 14, 1963 (Box 1)
  - October 16, 1963-November 11, 1963 (Box 1)
  - November 11, 1963- December 19, 1963 (Box 1)
  - December 27, 1963-January 24, 1964 (Box 1)
  - January 27, 1964-February 27, 1964 (Box 1)
  - February 28, 1964-March 31, 1964 (Box 1)
  - March 31, 1964-April 26, 1964 (Box 1)
  - April 24, 1964-May 18, 1964 (Box 1)
  - May 21, 1964-June 16, 1964 (Box 1)
  - June 17, 1964-July 28, 1964 (Box 1)
  - July 30, 1964-October 9, 1964 (Box 1)
  - October 9, 1964-October 30, 1964 (Box 1)
  - November 2, 1964- December 1, 1964 (Box 1)
  - December 3, 1964- December 31, 1964 (Box 1)
  - January 4, 1965- February 8, 1965 (Box 1)
  - February 12, 1965-March 2, 1965 (Box 1)
  - March 3, 1965- March 31, 1965 (Box 1)
  - April 1, 1965- April 26, 1965 (Box 1)
  - April 26, 1965- June 12, 1965 (Box 1)
  - May 12, 1965- June 17, 1965 (Box 1)
  - June 21, 1965- August 31, 1965 (Box 1)
  - September 1, 1965- October 11, 1965 (Box 1)
  - October 12, 1965- November 15, 1965 (Box 1)
  - November 16, 1965- December 30, 1965 (Box 1)
  - January 1, 1966- January 31, 1966 (Box 1)
  - February 6, 1966- March 15, 1966 (Box 1)
  - March 16, 1966- April 14, 1966 (Box 1)
  - April 15, 1966- May 3, 1966 (Box 1)
  - May 4, 1966- June 1, 1966 (Box 1)
  - June 1, 1966- June 16, 1966 (Box 1)
  - June 16, 1966- September 19, 1966 (Box 1)
  - September 20, 1966- October 10, 1966 (Box 1)
  - October 10, 1966- October 24, 1966 (Box 1)
  - October 23, 1966- November 11, 1966 (Box 2)
  - November 13, 1966- December 4, 1966 (Box 2)
  - December 11, 1966- January 9, 1967 (Box 2)
  - January 9, 1967- February 9, 1967 (Box 2)
  - February 10, 1967- March 7, 1967 (Box 2)
  - March 7, 1967- March 23, 1967 (Box 2)
  - April 3, 1967- April 25, 1967 (Box 2)
  - April 25, 1967- May 16, 1967 (Box 2)
  - May 17, 1967- June 20, 1967 (Box 2)
  - June 21, 1967- August 28, 1967 (Box 2)
  - August 30, 1967- October 10, 1967 (Box 2)
  - October 10, 1967- October 25, 1967 (Box 2)
  - October 26, 1967- November 14, 1967 (Box 2)
  - November 15, 1967- December 7, 1967 (Box 2)
  - December 10, 1967- January 23, 1968 (Box 2)
  - January 23, 1968- February 26, 1968 (Box 2)
  - February 27, 1968- March 15, 1968 (Box 2)
  - March 20, 1968- April 10, 1968 (Box 2)
  - April 11, 1968- May 2, 1968 (Box 2)
  - May 2, 1968- June 11, 1968 (Box 2)
  - June 11, 1968- August 21, 1968 (Box 2)
  - July 16, 1968- August 29, 1968 (Box 2)
  - August 21, 1968- September 25, 1968 (Box 2)
  - September 3, 1968- October 2, 1968 (Box 2)
  - September 26, 1968- October 16, 1968 (Box 2)
  - October 4, 1968- October 22, 1968 (Box 2)
  - October 17, 1968- October 30, 1968 (Box 2)
  - October 22, 1968- November 4, 1968 (Box 2)
  - October 29, 1968- November 8, 1968 (Box 2)
  - November 4, 1968- November 12, 1968 (Box 2)
  - November 8, 1968- November 14, 1968 (Box 2)
  - November 11, 1968- November 15, 1968 (Box 2)
  - November 14, 1968- November 27, 1968 (Box 2)
  - November 15, 1968- December 5, 1968 (Box 2)
  - December 4, 1968- December 6, 1968 (Box 2)
  - December 9, 1968- December 18, 1968 (Box 2)
  - December 4, 1968- December 26, 1968 (Box 2)
  - December 19, 1968- January 7, 1969 (Box 2)
  - January 2, 1969, January 16, 1969 (Box 2)
  - January 7, 1969- January 16, 1969 (Box 2)
  - January 16, 1969- January 17, 1969 (Box 2)
  - January 20, 1969- January 23, 1969 (Box 2)
  - January 24, 1969- February 3, 1969 (Box 2)
  - February 4, 1969- February 17, 1969 (Box 2)
  - February 18, 1969- February 26, 1969 (Box 2)
  - February 27, 1969- March 11, 1969 (Box 2)
  - March 11, 1969- March 28, 1969 (Box 3)
  - March 31, 1969- April 14, 1969 (Box 3)
  - April 16, 1969- April 18, 1969 (Box 3)
  - April 18, 1969- April 28, 1969 (Box 3)
  - April 29, 1969- May 6, 1969 (Box 3)
  - May 2, 1969- May 13, 1969 (Box 3)
  - May 14, 1969- May 29, 1969 (Box 3)
  - May 29, 1969 (Box 3)
  - May 29, 1969- June 9, 1969 (Box 3)
  - June 12, 1969- August 28, 1969 (Box 3)
  - August 29, 1969- September 18, 1969 (Box 3)
  - September 18, 1969- October 2, 1969 (Box 3)
  - October 2, 1969- October 14, 1969 (Box 3)
  - October 18, 1969- October 27, 1969 (Box 3)
  - October 28, 1969- November 5, 1969 (Box 3)
  - November 5, 1969- November 17, 1969 (Box 3)
  - November 21, 1969- December 1, 1969 (Box 3)
  - December 1, 1969- December 8, 1969 (Box 3)
  - December 8, 1969- December 19, 1969 (Box 3)
  - December 22, 1969- January 15, 1970 (Box 3)
  - January 15, 1970- January 29, 1970 (Box 3)
  - February 2, 1970- February 9, 1970 (Box 3)
  - February 8, 1970- February 13, 1970 (Box 3)
  - February 13, 1970- February 23, 1970 (Box 3)
  - February 23, 1970- March 9, 1970 (Box 3)
  - March 10, 1970- April 13, 1970 (Box 3)
  - April 13, 1970- April 22, 1970 (Box 3)
  - April 24, 1970- May 4, 1970 (Box 3)
  - May 5, 1970- May 15, 1970 (Box 3)
  - May 18, 1970- June 1, 1970 (Box 3)
  - June 1, 1970- June 12, 1970 (Box 3)
  - June 12, 1970- September 15, 1970 (Box 3)
  - September 16, 1970- October 6, 1970 (Box 3)
  - October 7, 1970- October 15, 1970 (Box 3)
  - October 20, 1970 (Box 3)
  - October 19, 1970- October 29, 1970 (Box 3)
  - November 4, 1970- November 17, 1970 (Box 3)
  - November 18, 1970- November 24, 1970 (Box 3)
  - November 25, 1970- December 9, 1970 (Box 3)
  - December 9, 1970 (Box 3)
  - December 14, 1970- January 6, 1971 (Box 3)
  - January 7, 1971- January 29, 1971 (Box 3)
  - February 9, 1971- February 19, 1971 (Box 3)
  - February 19, 1971- March 2, 1971 (Box 3)
  - March 2, 1971- March 9, 1971 (Box 3)
  - March 10, 1971- March 12, 1971 (Box 3)
  - March 16, 1971- March 22, 1971 (Box 3)
  - March 29, 1971- April 1, 1971 (Box 3)
  - April 1, 1971- April 12, 1971 (Box 3)
  - April 13, 1971- April 21, 1971 (Box 3)
  - April 22, 1971- April 27, 1971 (Box 3)
  - April 29, 1971- May 4, 1971 (Box 4)
  - May 4, 1971- May 10, 1971 (Box 4)
  - May 10, 1971- May 18, 1971 (Box 4)
  - May 18, 1971- May 20, 1971 (Box 4)
  - May 20, 1971- May 25, 1971 (Box 4)
  - May 25, 1971 (Box 4)
  - May 26, 1971- June 3, 1971 (Box 4)
  - June 5, 1971- June 24, 1971 (Box 4)
  - June 29, 1971- September 14, 1971 (Box 4)
  - September 14, 1971- September 23, 1971 (Box 4)
  - September 23, 1971- October 4, 1971 (Box 4)
  - October 5, 1971- October 18, 1971 (Box 4)
  - October 18, 1871- October 21, 1971 (Box 4)
  - October 22, 1971- October 28, 1971 (Box 4)
  - November 1, 1971- November 11, 1971 (Box 4)
  - November 11, 1971- November 29, 1971 (Box 4)
  - November 29, 1971- December 2, 1971 (Box 4)
  - December 6, 1971- January 3, 1972 (Box 4)
  - January 3, 1972- January 25, 1972 (Box 4)
  - January 26, 1972- February 8, 1972 (Box 4)
  - February 9, 1972- February 22, 1972 (Box 4)
  - February 22, 1972 (Box 4)
  - February 24, 1972- March 6, 1972 (Box 4)
  - March 7, 1972- March 15, 1972 (Box 4)
  - March 15, 1972- April 6, 1972 (Box 4)
  - April 7, 1972- April 25, 1972 (Box 4)
  - April 25, 1972- May 15, 1972 (Box 4)
  - May 15, 1972- May 24, 1972 (Box 4)
  - May 25, 1972- August 11, 1972 (Box 4)
  - August 27, 1972- September 14, 1972 (Box 4)
  - September 15, 1972- September 29, 1972 (Box 4)
  - October 2, 1972- October 4, 1972 (Box 4)
  - October 5, 1972- October 17, 1972 (Box 4)
  - October 18, 1972- November 1, 1972 (Box 4)
  - November 2, 1972- November 13, 1972 (Box 4)
  - November 14, 1972- November 28, 1972 (Box 4)
  - November 28, 1972- December 11, 1972 (Box 4)
  - December 12, 1972- January 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - January 19, 1973- February 1, 1973 (Box 4)
  - February 1, 1973- February 13, 1973 (Box 4)
  - February 13, 1973- February 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - February 19, 1973- March 2, 1973 (Box 4)
  - March 5, 1973- March 15, 1973 (Box 4)
  - March 15, 1973- April 4, 1973 (Box 4)
  - April 4, 1973- April 16, 1973 (Box 4)
  - May 4, 1973- May 23, 1973 (Box 4)
  - June 2, 1973- August 10, 1973 (Box 4)
  - August 13, 1973- September 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - September 20, 1973- September 27, 1973 (Box 4)
  - September 28, 1973- October 8, 1973 (Box 4)
  - October 8, 1973- October 16, 1973 (Box 4)
  - October 17, 1973- October 29, 1973 (Box 4)
  - October 29, 1973- November 9, 1973 (Box 4)
  - November 8, 1973- November 13, 1973 (Box 4)
  - November 14, 1973- November 20, 1973 (Box 4)
  - November 26, 1973- December 4, 1973 (Box 4)
  - December 5, 1973- December 21, 1973 (Box 4)
  - January 2, 1974, January 21, 1974 (Box 4)
  - January 21, 1974- February 5, 1974 (Box 5)
  - February 6, 1974- February 20, 1974 (Box 5)
  - February 21, 1974- February 28, 1974 (Box 5)
  - February 28, 1974- March 13, 1974 (Box 5)
  - March 14, 1974- April 1, 1974 (Box 5)
  - April 1, 1974- April 2, 1974 (Box 5)
  - April 2, 1974- April 3, 1974 (Box 5)
  - April 3, 1974- April 20, 1974 (Box 5)
  - April 22, 1974- May 2, 1974 (Box 5)
  - May 6, 1974- May 16, 1974 (Box 5)
  - May 16, 1974- May 24, 1974 (Box 5)
  - May 20, 1974- June 2, 1974 (Box 5)
  - May 28, 1974- June 2, 1974 (Box 5)
  - June 2, 1974 (three folders) (Box 5)
  - June 2, 1974- June 26, 1974 (Box 5)
  - July 1, 1974- September 6, 1974 (Box 5)
  - September 8, 1974- September 16, 1974 (Box 5)
  - September 16, 1974 (Box 5)
  - September 16, 1974- September 18, 1974 (Box 5)
  - September 16, 1974- October 4, 1974 (Box 5)
  - September 30, 1974- October 15, 1974 (Box 5)
  - October 14, 1974- October 25, 1974 (Box 5)
  - October 27, 1974- November 10, 1974 (Box 5)
  - November 4, 1974- November 13, 1974 (Box 5)
  - November 14, 1974- November 25, 1974 (Box 5)
  - November 25, 1974- December 10, 1974 (Box 5)
  - December 13, 1974 (Box 5)
  - December 16, 1974- December 26, 1974 (Box 5)
  - January 2, 1975- January 13, 1975 (Box 5)
  - January 11, 1975- January 28, 1975 (Box 5)
  - January 29, 1975- February 11, 1975 (Box 5)
  - February 13, 1975- February 18, 1975 (Box 5)
  - February 19, 1975- February 24, 1975 (Box 5)
  - February 26, 1975- March 7, 1975 (Box 5)
  - March 10, 1975- March 18, 1975 (Box 5)
  - March 18, 1975- March 20, 1975 (Box 5)
  - March 19, 1975- April 3, 1975 (Box 5)
  - April 4, 1975- April 18, 1975 (Box 5)
  - April 9, 1975- April 25, 1975 (Box 5)
  - April 29, 1975- May 13, 1975 (Box 5)
  - May 13, 1975- May 15, 2975 (Box 5)
  - May 15, 1975- May 23, 1975 (Box 5)
  - May 21, 1975- May 23, 1975 (Box 5)
  - May 27, 1975- June 11, 1975 (Box 5)
  - June 11, 1975 (three folders) (Box 5)
  - June 12, 1975- June 18, 1975 (Box 5)
  - July 22, 1975- August 9, 1975 (Box 5)
  - September 1, 1975- September 17, 1975 (Box 5)
  - September 17, 1975- September 23, 1975 (Box 5)
  - September 19, 1975- September 30, 1975 (Box 5)
  - September 26, 1975- October 4, 1975 (Box 5)
  - October 1, 1975- October 10, 1975 (Box 5)
  - October 2, 1975- October 17, 1975 (Box 5)
  - October 11, 1975- October 20, 1975 (Box 6)
  - October 15, 1975- October 22, 1975 (Box 6)
  - October 22, 1975- October 27, 1975 (Box 6)
  - October 24, 1975- October 30, 1975 (Box 6)
  - October 31, 1975- November 12, 1975 (Box 6)
  - October 28, 1975- November 7, 1975 (Box 6)
  - November 7, 1975- November 11, 1975 (Box 6)
  - November 11, 1975 (two folders) (Box 6)
  - November 11, 1975- November 15, 1975 (Box 6)
  - November 12, 1975- November 17, 1975 (Box 6)
  - November 19, 1975- November 26, 1975 (Box 6)
  - November 19, 1975- December 1, 1975 (Box 6)
  - November 29, 1975- December 8, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 2, 1975- December 12, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 8, 1975- December 17, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 8, 1975- December 17, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 17, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 17, 1975- December 30, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 18, 1975 (Box 6)
  - December 28, 1975- January 12, 1976 (Box 6)
  - January 5, 1976- January 16, 1976 (Box 6)
  - January 15, 1976- January 23, 1975 (Box 6)
  - January 22, 1976- February 1, 1976 (Box 6)
  - January 22, 1976- January 30, 1976 (Box 6)
  - January 29, 1976- February 30, 1976 (Box 6)
  - February 2, 1976- February 20, 1976 (Box 6)
  - February 9, 1976- February 21, 1976 (Box 6)
  - February 22, 1976- February 29, 1976 (Box 6)
  - February 14, 1976- February 27, 1976 (Box 6)
  - February 25, 1976- March 13, 1976 (Box 6)
  - March 1, 1976- March 26, 1976 (Box 6)
  - March 17, 1976- March 27, 1976 (Box 6)
  - March 18, 1976 (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - March 23, 1976- March 30, 1976 (Box 6)
  - March 25, 1976- April 2, 1976 (Box 6)
  - March 30, 1976- April 11, 1976 (Box 6)
  - March 30, 1976- April 7, 1976 (Box 6)
  - April 8, 1976- April 17, 1976 (Box 6)
  - April 12, 1976- April 23, 1976 (Box 6)
  - April 15, 1976- May 1, 1976 (Box 6)
  - April 17, 1976- April 30, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 1, 1976- May 14, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 3, 1976- May 11, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 5, 1976- May 23, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 12, 1976- May 30, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 21, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 21, 1976- May 26, 1976 (Box 6)
  - May 26, 1976 (three folders) (Box 6)
  - May 30, 1976 (eight folders) (Box 6)
  - June 1, 1976- June 18, 1976 (Box 7)
  - June 3, 1976- June 22, 1976 (Box 7)
  - June 21, 1976- July 7, 1976 (Box 7)
  - June 22, 1976- July 16, 1976 (Box 7)
  - July 8, 1976- July 23, 1976 (Box 7)
  - July 20, 1976 (two folders) (Box 7)
  - July 20, 1976- July 23, 1976 (Box 7)
  - July 23, 1976- September 1, 1976 (Box 7)
  - July 23, 1976- September 1, 1976 (Box 7)
  - September 8, 1976- September 18, 1976 (Box 7)
  - September 8, 1976- September 21, 1976 (Box 7)
  - September 20, 1976- September 27, 1976 (Box 7)
  - September 22, 1976- September 27, 1976 (Box 7)
  - September 27, 1976 (two folders) (Box 7)
  - September 27, 1976- 29, 1976 (Box 7)
  - September 30, 1976-October 9, 1976 (Box 7)
  - October 2, 1976- October 25, 1976 (Box 7)
  - October 11, 1976- October 18, 1976 (Box 7)
  - October 20, 1976- October 30, 1976 (Box 7)
  - October 25, 1976- November 16, 1976 (Box 7)
  - November 2, 1976- November 10, 1976 (Box 7)
  - November 11, 1976- December 4, 1976 (Box 7)
  - November 24, 1976- December 17, 1976 (Box 7)
  - December 1, 1976- December 14, 1976 (Box 7)
  - December 17, 1976- December 21, 1976 (Box 7)
  - December 21, 1976- January 5, 1977 (Box 7)
  - December 30, 1976- January 5, 1977 (Box 7)
  - January 3, 1977- January 18, 1977 (Box 7)
  - January 3, 1977- January 22, 1977 (Box 7)
  - January 18, 1977- January 28, 1977 (Box 7)
  - January 20, 1977- February 2, 1977 (Box 7)
  - January 27, 1977- February 5, 1977 (Box 7)
  - February 2, 1977- February 10, 1977 (Box 7)
  - February 7, 1977- February 12, 1977 (Box 7)
  - February 12, 1977- February 28, 1977 (Box 7)
  - February 15, 1977- February 23, 1977 (Box 7)
  - February 25, 1977- March 23, 1977 (Box 7)
  - March 1, 1977- March 23, 1977 (Box 7)
  - March 21, 1977- March 29, 1977 (Box 7)
  - March 22, 1977- March 29, 1977 (Box 7)
  - March 29, 1977- April 9, 1977 (Box 7)
  - March 29, 1977- April 6, 1977 (Box 7)
  - April 7, 1977- April 16, 1977 (Box 7)
  - April 11, 1977- April 19, 1977 (Box 7)
  - April 20, 1977- April 21, 1977 (Box 7)
  - April 22, 1977- May 7, 1977 (Box 7)
  - May 9, 1977- May 19, 1977 (Box 7)
  - May 19, 1977 (four folders) (Box 7)
  - May 28, 1977 (Box 7)
  - May 29, 1977 (two folders) (Box 7)
  - June 1, 1977- July 24, 1977 (Box 7)
  - July 27, 1977- September 13, 1977 (Box 7)
  - September 15, 1977- October 1, 1977 (Box 7)
  - October 3, 1977- October 18, 1977 (Box 7)
  - October 19, 1977- November 1, 1977 (Box 7)
  - October 31, 1977- November 12, 1977 (Box 8)
  - November 14, 1977- November 29, 1977 (Box 8)
  - December 3, 1977- January 9, 1978 (Box 8)
  - January 10, 1978- February 17, 1978 (Box 8)
  - February 10, 1978- February 18, 1978 (Box 8)
  - February 21, 1978- March 21, 1978 (Box 8)
  - March 21, 1978- April 4, 1978 (Box 8)
  - April 5, 1978- April 12, 1978 (Box 8)
  - April 13, 1978- May 1, 1978 (Box 8)
  - May 2, 1978- May 17, 1978 (Box 8)
  - May 16, 1978- May 28, 1978 (Box 8)
  - May 28, 1978 (Box 8)
  - May 28, 1978- June 20, 1978 (Box 9)
  - June 23, 1978- July 21, 1978 (Box 9)
  - July 24, 1978- August 3, 1978 (Box 9)
  - August 3, 1978 (Box 9)
  - August 7, 1978- September 16, 1978 (Box 9)
  - September 19, 1978- October 12, 1978 (Box 9)
  - October 14, 1978- October 26, 1978 (Box 9)
  - October 26, 1978- November 4, 1978 (Box 9)